[
  {
    "question": "sit",
    "answer": "sat"
  },
  {
    "question": "speak",
    "answer": "spoke"
  },
  {
    "question": "lie",
    "answer": "lay"
  },
  {
    "question": "lead",
    "answer": "led"
  },
  {
    "question": "read",
    "answer": "read"
  },
  {
    "question": "grow",
    "answer": "grew"
  },
  {
    "question": "lose",
    "answer": "lost"
  },
  {
    "question": "fall",
    "answer": "fell"
  },
  {
    "question": "send",
    "answer": "sent"
  },
  {
    "question": "build",
    "answer": "built"
  },
  {
    "question": "understand",
    "answer": "understood"
  },
  {
    "question": "draw",
    "answer": "drew"
  },
  {
    "question": "break",
    "answer": "broke"
  },
  {
    "question": "spend",
    "answer": "spent"
  },
  {
    "question": "cut",
    "answer": "cut"
  },
  {
    "question": "rise",
    "answer": "rose"
  },
  {
    "question": "drive",
    "answer": "drove"
  },
  {
    "question": "buy",
    "answer": "bought"
  },
  {
    "question": "wear",
    "answer": "wore"
  },
  {
    "question": "choose",
    "answer": "chose"
  }
]